Seino!
GARUGARU CHANNEL Concord!
Yay!
Today!
Three, two, one!
Watermelon Split!
Tension!
Which way? Which way?
Three, two, one!
Summer project!
What are you doing?
Ready!
Watermelon splitting!
You're making me say it so much!
What?
Let's get to it!
Let's go!
It's so short!
It's short.
I've never done this before.
So please lower your stance now.
Wait, this is it.
We'll have to come all the way down here.
That camera's not rolling.
Is it rolling?
Can I take it now?
I mean, who's gonna do it then?
I'm blindfolded.
I agree. Let's play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
There's no winners in this.
Everyone has to work together.
If everyone cracks it open, we can eat it.
Whoever wins gets to crack it open and enjoy the taste.
Let's eat it together.
Okay, let's get ready. Let's decide.
First, goo, then rock, paper, scissors.First goo, then rock, paper, scissors
First goo, then rock, paper, scissors.
First, goo, rock-paper-scissors, rock-paper-scissors.
I'll go first.
Can I help you with this?
I'll help you if it's dangerous.
Right, right, right.
You want me to turn it by myself?
I don't know about the center.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'll take five.
Okay, okay.
Come here, come here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can you say right?
Straight, straight.
Right, right, right, right, right.
Right, right.
Left.
Ready?
What?
It's broken.
Is it that soft? Isn't watermelon amazing?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
After the first trial, there's nothing left to do.
Yum!
I still want to have fun.
Oops!
I thought you fixed it.
Yes, yes, 10 alguém.
Yes, yes, yes.
Here you go.
Watch out.
A little more.
Straight ahead.Straight ahead
Left
early
left, down
Ah!
They're all cracked.
It's all cracked.
How successful is this?
Deep?
It's on the left.
I don't know how you do it.
Where are your bangs?
Okay, let's go, Tou-chan.
No, you're early.
Two, three.
It's a little bit dangerous.
Grandma!
Grandma?
Oh, no.
Nine.
Ten.
Yes!
It's like granny's frosted ice.
Like my grandma's feet.
This way, this way.
Left, left.
That's right, left.
Let's go.
Ready?
Aren't you guys good?
Why is that?
How can they all do it?
The sound.
This feeling.
It's as good as I thought it would be.That's as good as it gets.
I was right, in case you were wondering.
I was right.
Everyone is so good.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Still 10
Yes good luck.
Dot go?
This way.
Go ahead.
Forward.
A little to the right.
There. A little more forward.
OK, OK. Ready.
Weak. Weak.
OK, weak.
It's not even broken. It was right on top of me.
That's amazing. Momochan and the others. Nothing's broken.
The first time in my life I broke a watermelon. It didn't break. It didn't break.
Watermelon is now. Watermelon?
Where did it hit? It hit here.
Oh, this one. I didn't break it.
It didn't break. I just hit it.
Hard enough to see the red.
Yes. Then, if you can't do it, I'll take my revenge, To-chan.
One, two, three.
Forward. Forward. Forward. Go. Go. Go.Yes, front. Front. Forward. Go. Go. Go.
Right. Right?
Turn left.
Too far. Too far. Right.
OK, OK. Ready.
It hit and cracked a little.
It cracked a little. It's broken.
Can I go a little further? Can you go?
Ready.
One more time, just like that. Go.
Go, go, go, go. One more time.
One more time.
Harder. Again.
One more time. Put your renewed energy into it.
I'm going.
A little more. A little more. Go. Go.
One more time. One more time.
Ready.
One more time.
It cracked. Liquid came out.
That's great. I'm hitting it pretty hard.
It's cracking really hard.
Then, I'll call it a success.
Oh, wow. Success.
Let's eat.
Amazing.
Wow! There's some left.
Oh no. It's really broken.
It's good.
Wow!
So...
Let's toast to the fact that it's cracked.
Cheers!
Cheers.
Bon appétit!Bon appétit.
Mmm.
Delicious.
Yum!
It's so good!
You know how watermelons taste so good with salt on them?
Yes, I know.
I always put salt on it.
Oh, wow.
I mean, isn't it, like, right here? Not this part? You put salt on it?
Oh, really? You put it on from the beginning?
From the beginning.
When it gets to this point, it tastes weak.
That's why I thought you put salt on it.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
Do you eat watermelon every year at home?
Oh, we already eat watermelon, Yooka.
But this is my first Wiley bar. I think it's the first time in my life.
I can't remember.
Stop huffing. Stop huffing.
We're not at home, so why don't we just huff and puff like we do at home? Right here.
I'm pretty sure that's where you're huffing and puffing.
There are still lots of watermelons alive. I'm sorry.
It's delicious. Watermelon is so sweet.
Yippee! So...
How was your first watermelon splitting?
Well, I'm glad I got to make a summer memory before I turned 20. It was delicious.
But I think I'd like to try it in the ocean next time.
I'm sure you're right. I have a strong image of the ocean.
On the beach. With Jaycee.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. It's a lot of work, but I'd love to do it.
Isn't it amazing? I made a mistake.
Well, you did it, Toa. How did you do it?
Well, it was difficult. My eyes were spinning.
So, I hope you enjoy your summer!So, I hope you all enjoy your summer!
Go to the next summer project!
Okay, so we're going to continue with the shaved ice.
We'll be having shaved ice in a few minutes.
We have strawberry, blue Hawaii, and lemon.
And the fruits?
We have blueberry, grapefruit, peach, mica, and pineapple.
And do you have any lemmings?
Yes, we do.
Is it the other way around? This one.
Just water?
I can't get on board.
What the hell is this?
I'm up! I'm up!
It's happening!
Is that shaved ice?
Oh, my God!
It's shaved ice!
It's on.
So, Kiku, do you buy shaved ice at festivals?
I like it.
I do.
What flavor do you buy?
Coke.
Wow!
Strawberry
Coke shaved ice
Wow, that doesn't make any sense.
Coke. That's good.
I'm not buying it. Why not?
When I say I'm not buying it, I really mean it's been 10 years.
I haven't had shaved ice in about 10 years.
It's nice to see shaved ice on the Galgal Channel for the first time in 10 years.
Yes, I'm happy.
I don't eat shaved ice.I don't eat shaved ice. I don't eat shaved ice.
I don't eat shaved ice.
It's done.
You're doing great.
I'll try it at my place.
It's been too long since I've felt this way.
That's good.
Oh, man.
I've been living on my own,
I did something hot.
I've been making somen noodles a lot lately.
I don't make it, I just boil it.
That's good.
May I make some?
Sure, go ahead.
I don't know. It's not good.
What do you want?
A frothy one, right?
Yes. Condensed milk?
Is that all you got?
You need more condensed milk.
Yes, sir.
There we go.
What's that? Huh? Huh?
It started biting right from the start.
Oh, wow.
Quick, quick, quick.
Fast, fast, fast.
It's over.
What? Huh?
Too fast!
The ice must be bad. It's melting.
Hang in there, hang in there.
It's okay.All right.
No way.
It's soaking wet.
Wait, there's a really nice dry sound.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
Okay, okay, okay.
It's soaking wet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's that? Strawberries.
Hey, guys.
I thought...
I thought the three of us would use it.
I thought Yuuki would like strawberries, too.
I wondered if she'd leave some for me.
Okay, Blue Fight.
I don't like it.
I'll have lemon.
I've never seen lemon.
You've never seen it.
I think I like Blue Hawaii a lot.
Why not Blue Hawaii?
I knew it. Strawberry.
That looks delicious.
Here, I'll give you some.
It's beautiful!
It's nice.
And all this space for glitter.
Hey, hey, hey.
Is that it?
It's so good.
It's like I ate it.
Why? It's so good.
It's good.
I don't like the way you put it on.
Why not? You're gonna complain.Why? You're gonna complain.
Are you filming this?
He told me I had a problem with the way you put me in the car.
I'll take one.
Bon appétit.
It's delicious.
It's good.
What do you think, Beeze?
What do you think of the taste of the mixture?
It doesn't taste so good.
Yum!
It's not shaved ice anymore.
Your favorite street food, then.
Mmm, good.
Wow, two of these.
That's your favorite one. Food.
It's definitely the food.
Okay.
Yakisoba.
Two yakisoba.
Yakisoba!
Ika-yaki, with meat rolls.
I know yakisoba!
I know what you mean about ikayaki.
Ika-yaki is something you can only get at a street stall.
They don't sell it?
That's right.
Yakisoba from a street stall...
I know.
I wonder why.
Do you go to festivals in yukata?
Or do you go in plain clothes?
It's cool like this.
I've never worn a yukata, fried bakingI've never worn a yukata. Fried baking.
Really?
Yeah. - Really?
I have an image of a yukata.
I have one myself.
Yeah, I have one, and I'd definitely wear it if I went to Asakusa or something.
Really?
I only wear it on those occasions.
You never wear it in private?
No.
Maybe in elementary school.
Uh...
I don't know.
But... yukata...
Until last year, I bought one as wallpaper for the fan club.
I had a chance to wear a yukata.
But this year it was at the beach.
That's right.
I wonder if they have yukatas.
I think so.
Ooh.
It's some kind of yukata where you walk around in a yukata and wear an amazing outfit for once.
It's in Miyazaki.
Yeah. Inside the event?
Yeah.
You put something red right here on your forehead, and then you put it right here.
Oh, yeah.
It's traditional.
Uh...
I'm just making fun of you.
No, no, no, no.
I've done that before.
How's the shaved ice, Kuya?
Oh, it's okay.
It's okay.so-so
So-so, so-so, so-so.
Don't say so-so with a strawberry.
What? It's a little...
I've had enough.
It's been a while since I had shaved ice.
Or not.
It's the first shaved ice of the year.
Right?
First time.
Then it's your first shaved ice of the year on the skinny channel.
And watermelon splitting.
That's for sure!
Who split the watermelon?
The two of us.
I'm glad we got to eat both watermelon and shaved ice!
Thank you for watching!
If you like this video, please click the "Good" button, subscribe to the channel, and leave a comment!
Bye bye!
This time we are wearing costumes by D-Holic!